There was something money couldn't buy
Yo!
Good night!
It's morning!
Himekawa Tatsuya...
One of Ishiyama's TKKH and the son
of the head of the Himekawa Group,
he lives by the motto "There ain't nothin'
that can't be controlled by money."
Himekawa-san, the thing you asked for.
Ah, I see.
Good work.
But lately, he's been in a fierce battle
with one who won't be swayed by money.
Ah, yes.
That's the way. Get around
20 people, that should do.
Don't worry, I'll pay.
I might have gotten beat by
that bullishly honest dolt,
but not this time...
I'll work behind the scenes, find out
your weakness, make careful preparations,
and this time for sure,
box you into a corner!
I have something you don't that
decides everything in the end...
That's right! The ultimate
weapon called money!
Oga! I'll send you to the pits of hell,
so you can never make a fool of me again!
School Shop
Hungry, Baby Beel?
Not yet(mada), then? I see...
Lady!
Right, that'll be 150 yen.
Huh? Where's the usual lady?
Oh... Sato-san's caught a cold today.
I'm her replacement.
So you are hungry?
Sheesh, fine then...
The shop lady's sick?
A cold that can take her
out's somethin' serious.
Lucky you. "Stupid people never catch colds."
I'm not stupid! I'm the
Strategist, remember?!
I've worked my magic behind the
scenes at the school shop...
I needed the lady to stay
quiet for a little while.
Now bite into my trap, Oga!
There's all kinds of stuff you ain't
never supposed to eat in that sandwich!
I don't care what you are, Oga,
ain't no one that can withstand an
attack from inside your stomach!
Hey.
You forgot the master's lunch.
What?!
Oh, my bad.
And your lunch as well, knave.
My lunch?
I've been told to make you eat
food from the Demon World.
Huh?
This is a Macao-style lunch I
made together with Hilda-chan.
(Lunch from your love! Ufu *heart* )
"Ufu" my ass!
This is really creepy, damn her!
What?!
Damn you, Oga's wife!
Man, I'm jealous! A lunch
made special by Hilda-san!
You want it?
What? Seriously?
Hilda-san, can I?
Suit yourself, Annoichi.
Sure. I already bought a sandwich.
Here you go, Annoichi.
Don't mind if I do!
Good job, Annoichi!
This is Hilda-san's handmade lunch!
It's a lunch of love!
I depart now, my cute wife, Hilda.
So long too, Akbaba Jr.
W-Wait!
Furuichi-san, here's your lunch!
Now now, Hilda... I've told you to
call me Takayuki-chan, remember?
You silly thing.
I put in your favorite
fried egg, Takayuki-chan!
Well, I'll look forward to it.
You're so cute, Hilda...
I love you... *smooch*
Furuichi, you're makin' a Demon quiver...
Y-You disgust me.
O-Oga... You can hear what I'm thinking?!
Sure, since you said it all out loud.
Anyway, thanks for the food!
I figured.
What'd you put in there today?
Fried pieces of silky Demon manjuuheel,
stewed Demon eel-mushroom,
and Demon black widow
omelet with green onions.
Are you trying to kill me or something?
Here, master...
Man...
Okay, all filled up!
How's the taste of the
Demon World, Furuichi-kun?
Why? Why isn't he suffering?
You actually ate this stuff?
And thanks to it, my stomach's
stronger than ever!
That stomach of yours ain't normal, man!
Whatever... On to the next plan.
Himekawa...
What the hell have you done?
Ishiyama Market Street.
What's this?
There's a ton of costumed
animal characters...
He'll actually pay us that bonus, right?
That's right! Whoever catches Oga's
brat gets their pay plus a bonus!
I'll catch him, even if it costs me my life!
Mr. Rabbit!
Mr. Bear!
Mr. Kappa!
Shoo!
Seriously.
You're so not a cute baby.
You wanna go, buddy?
It's Gohan-kun!
You know who that is!
You know... that!
Eat Rice!
The world-renown shounen
manga even you read...
The immortal, legendary work that's
passed its 50th anniversary!
With an anime that gets TV ratings higher than
20%... Truly Japan's national treasure, Gohan-kun!
Said to be nothing else like it
ever created in the entire world...
Why would a costumed character of Gohan-kun
be here in Ishiyama Market Street?!
Oga... My target is that
baby stuck to your back.
If I could take that baby hostage,
even you wouldn't be able to act!
I don't care if you call this underhanded...
I'll use whatever methods I can!
That's right! Take the bait!
While the baby is distracted
by the character...
A pen, a pen! Where'd I put it?
That damn Gohan-kun...
He found them first!
Hold it, Gohan! Wait
right there, you bastard!
This way, Gohan-kun! Your autograph, please!
Oga...
Explosive Uppercut!
Oga! What the hell have you done?!
He was a fake.
The real one's chopsticks
are red on the ends.
But his were yellow.
Man, he don't spare anyone.
Damn, I underestimated him.
I still have more plans...
Two fist croquette, please.
I'll have one.
Sure thing.
Here you go, fresh out of the fryer.
Hot!
We'll wait for them to
cool, so hold on a sec.
Hey, young lad.
That baby is so cute...
May I hold him for a moment?
If you let me, then next, I'll hold
you, my strapping young man...
Y-Y-Y-You'll hold me?!
The previous two plans failed,
but this one's foolproof!
A dynamite body even better than Oga's
wife, overflowing with maternal instinct!
A baby can't help but
be completely entranced!
Ma'am!
Furuichi-dono!
Even though you have me, you would obsess
over such an odd creature as this?!
Stop, please!
For god's sake please stop showing
up out of the blue like that!
And hey, that's rude calling
her an odd creature!
Then look at this!
It's a delinquent dressed up like a lady!
Too bad we were found out.
I guess we'll just crush
everyone at once then!
Since it has come to this, Furuichi-dono,
enter my body once again!
Comeback Salmon!
What the...
Transfer.
We should be able to eat 'em soon.
Ah, well.
Hey, lady! Give us two that
aren't just out of the fryer!
Why me, too?!
Now, let us return home, Furuichi-dono!
Transfer!
Whoa, there... What the hell is this...
Remaining Balance: 0 yen
I'm out of money.
I've never been out of money my entire life.
Maybe I did use a little too much...
Allowance: 10,000,000 yen.
Information Gathering: 10,000 yen.
The fees for the extras
this episode: 300,000 yen.
Store Lady double: 30,000 yen.
Costume Character Setup: 4,200,000 yen.
Plus the pay for the performers
inside: 250,000 yen.
The pay for the guy dressed
up as a girl: 30,000 yen.
Cost of escape from deserted
island: 5,000,000 yen.
Plus miscellaneous expenses: 180,000 yen.
Remaining Allowance: 0 yen
Until I get my allowance next month I'm
gonna have to get by with no money!
This is all that damn Oga's fault...
Screw him! I'll never forgive this!
Perfect timing.
You, go to Oga and...
Sorry about this, Himekawa-san,
but can you pay up front?
What did you say?!
Well, I've been thinking a lot, see...
I really need to think more about
compliance and risk management issues.
This is a dangerous bridge to cross, so
considering the actuality of risk, a PDC cycle would...
I don't know what you're talking about!
Well, not like I was planning
on hiring you anyway!
Crap...
Hey, you!
Oh, Himekawa-san...
You, there! Go to Oga and...
Hell, no, man.
I'm so scared of the old lady at the
shop that I can't buy from her anymore!
What am I supposed to do for
lunch until I graduate now?
You're annoying. Why don't
you just order delivery?
Sure thing. Right after
you hand me cash for it.
Sheesh, they're all such...
Hey, Hime-chan.
Whatcha doin' here?
It's rare to see you alone.
Oh, shut up.
So, why do you guys follow
an idiot like Kanzaki?
It's a long story.
This isn't the place to tell you.
I've decided to stick with
him, no matter what happens...
What about you, Natsume?
A guy like you doesn't have to
follow someone like Kanzaki...
For me, it's because I find it amusing.
I want to be wherever is
most interesting to me.
Kanzaki-kun is really active, so it's fun.
Some extra activity, and you'll
be more fun too, Hime-chan.
If there is ever a time you feel you've lost
your way, you must ask your heart once more...
Now, Shiro-chan, we need
to go buy that yogurty.
So, should I just go crush Oga myself, then?
But, I don't have any money.
So for now...
I'll throw everything I got left at
him! Even Oga wouldn't be able to...
Well, Oga's stomach is bearishly
strong, after all...
I think I'll quit while I'm ahead.
Didn't you see? I was in big trouble!
Here they come...
Okay. If it hadn't been for them
noticing this small difference...
This time, I'll get that baby!
Explosive Uppercut!
Hey, two cooled fist croquette, please.
I'll take one.
You two come every day. Thanks a bunch.
Here. These are cooled down.
T-This time...
I still got this left!
That damn Oga... We're gonna bust him up good!
Don't feel you gotta hold
back! We're all his victims!
Who the hell are you?!
Hey, you. What the hell do you think
you're trying to do on Ishiyama's turf?
H-Himekawa!
Crap...
What? You alone?
Where's the posse you
always have with you, huh?
They run away, eh?
Your pals all ditched you, huh?
What a loser!
How 'bout you join our team, Himekawa-san?
Well, he can't do nothin' by himself.
That might be true.
But I'm not a member of the TKKH
just from the power of money alone.
Why, you...
Take that!
This is what you get for buttin'
your head in where it don't belong!
Die, all of you!
Damn him...
You bastard...
This bazooka was for our
anti-Oga plan, but too bad...
This is Oga's job... It
ain't my style, damn it!
What was that?
Yo. You awake?
Have a drink?
I don't feel like drinkin' your backwash.
The vending machine broke, so two came out.
I was just gonna throw it out anyway.
This is why you weren't raised right...
Don't waste food, you!
Oh, yeah?
I think you'd make me a
pretty nice trash bin.
This ain't bad.
See?
Go buy me some every day.
How about you apologize for
gettin' a big head, huh?
Why don't we just find out
who should be apologizin'?
Oh, yeah?!
Nothing's happened lately, you know?
Well, as long as you can call
picking up a baby Demon Lord,
having a demon maidservent show up,
and having a burly transference
demon squat at my house "nothing".
Baby Beel, let's go buy one more croquette.
You guys are real gluttons!
I don't like bein' in anyone's debt.
For you, penniless little fellow,
a one year's supply of yogurty.
What the hell is this?!
Kanzaki-kun, all of these have expiration
dates a month from now, so please be careful.
Why, you...
Natsume, Shiroyama... Do something!
Let me outta here!
Baby Beel's crying so loud
at night, I can't sleep!
Then we'll use a home remedy!
Drink a glass of water
while holding your nose!
That's how to stop hiccups!
On the next Beelzebub: I
won't let you sleep tonight!
Then should I go with the old standby of
counting camel crickets jumping over a fence?!
Camel crickets? Scary!