You guys really embarrassing ah
But in any case you want to know if you can tell a good
Fast ride good good listen
long long ago…
In fact, it is not so long
Shortly before that thing
City monsters everywhere in the world
One of the most popular is the astringent Day Street
In this valley like Suribachi lived ten million monster
Guide their years of monster guru claimed to retire
God and reincarnation
Is considering to become what God
Once you have decided
Will elect a new master
So we told to be ready
Successor condition is the strength and character of every class
Then the first to be nominated
King of the Mountain is a monster called a pig
Calm of courage
Is a strong man with a large number of disciples
Koizumi also Jiro Yan and the father of two sons pill
The next generation of master must go to him
We are so word of mouth
But there is another monster in the reserve candidate in
Toru named Bear
Renruqiming a bear figure
Motion-sensitive monkey general
And endless stamina
Vigorously waving proud sword
Everyone says
Light said power if he is above the pig Wang Shan
Anyway he is a tricky guy
Pride also bear rude unruly selfish
Not a disciple
The more impossible to have a son
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
Do not touch me stop
You are a minor, right
Nah
Ran away from home right
Say that not ah
little mouse? still is…
Good small ah
Wait
Come
Eat
From where you are to escape it?
I was alone
Carried there
Yes
Start here to start
Dad where are you now?
what are you doing?
Why do not you do this time?
The lotus is almost gone
The ... how to do this?
Ah that we move it
Your mother died suddenly Lin
You might be lonely
But, after all, so there is no way accidents
You will be led away capitalists guardian
do you understand
You are our family, only boys
It is important heir
Since then allow you the freedom to grow
Lin understand, give me soon as promised
Why did not my father come?
Quickly forget that guy, right
why? Dad is Dad
You know the man and mom divorced, right?
The court awarded custody of the side
You and he has absolutely no relationship
I live on a person
Blind children say
A person how you live
A person to live to see you
I want to become stronger Zhengkou Qi give you a look
How you speak
Lin you ...
Most annoying!
Whether you or Dad
Are the most annoying!
Stop lotus lotus
The most annoying ...
The most annoying
Hate hate
Most hated
Most annoying!
The most annoying ... ...
Qi can
I'm fine thanks
What is hateful in the end ah
Anyway, it is better than the pig Wang Shanqiang it Well
Character? Totally do not understand
Guru is really nonsense ah
Before you guys in there just long before fleeing out?
One week a month ...?
one day…
One morning a morning ah!
I hate crying Ghosts!
Now is the right time to pick and choose
The human side of the broom or brush what caught as a disciple
Okay so ah
Hello I do not really joking ah
Hey
I say hello
You guys in the end is dead or alive ah
Sick of it
Can speak is still alive 1,10
Where's your mother
That your dad
To shut up
Answer me your dad
Shut up shut up shut up shut up
Again and I'll kill you speak
What a mere kid actor Jae Jae ah
Let me take a look at your face
Strange ... strange ...
monster
Enough of it
Do you want to come with me?
what? What are you talking nonsense you bear thorough!
That is just what ...
I say you are not away from home?
Put ... Let me go!
A person is not a night out, oh boy
let me go
Your guardian phone number?
Let him go back to pick you up
Do not
Well over
Absolutely ... Do not!
Stop feeding
stop
Hey! Hey!
Which ran the run gone?
Not here
Here it is really Shibuya
it hurts
Strange how could this just did not come the way
Export export it ...
let me go
Is a human child
Why here
Just
The skin chops it shop sold shamisen
After it dried to make dried fish dry pine
still is…
Help save
what?
Not to mention such a sinful words
Tut what a great ...
No do not worry
Those guys mouth and looks just a little insane point
Do not be afraid
I patchouli Square
As you can see I am a spiritual person
Wanted to come here astringent Day Street
Have to go to reach the particular route
We can become God and God can not be human
The world we live in is different
Occasionally lost in. You must be very upset it
I'll take you back to the original world
Yo You guys really coming
As I expected
I really like you more and more
Come
what are you going to do
He was just a lost child
You can not point to his gentle yet
tender?
Monk is really silly naive ah
Is so you do not manhandle mean
What's wrong with the use of brute force
He is not a lost child
This guy from now on is my disciple
Did not I say the thing you forget it
You want the human child received as a disciple it
I do not care is a human or brush broom
I said that disciple disciple!
Wait inferior inferior
I do not say how many times the
Tatara you explain
When the master said to be the successor to the words
Anyway have received a disciple
But the king of the mountains, not to mention the pig
There is no one willing to do this guy's disciple
And then he went to those poor humans when
Found this kid actor
So you put him over the Abduction
His own with over
Can not even say nothing to those who dragged
I can not promote some promising people do
It recklessly ah
So those who want to inherit this seat, please
This guy does not just want to win the King of the Mountain pig Bale
What then becomes reincarnated master to God
He has no interest in it
Even if this guy is the reincarnation
At most it is tsukumogami
Toilet brush broom God or what God
Poor is the human child ah
Toru together and bear it really does not matter
Who knows anyway, I do not know
Disciples in the end is how is it
I said I support you from now
I did not ask you
But I hate crybaby
Cry, then it flew to throw you out
But I do not remember you promised to become disciples
Why else would you come with
why…
Do not say I know
Homelessness is not it
I do sympathize with you
And other such things that you can work independently to say blind say
Anyway you can only live for one person
Do not ask your name
what?
Because it is personal privacy
what! That age it
Then you too from now on called the nine
Why should you give me a name ah
Do you understand it is called nine too
So I want to sleep ah nine too
lotus
I did what you like plus ham omelet
Eat hot
Ok
Well escape ah
I knew this would happen
Found the
time to eat
stop
Still angry ah
I opened a little joke
Well eat fast
Raw not wasted
Do not say you're not hungry
I'm hungry
Raw eggs or something
Too fishy can not eat
So eat
what did you say
Good dirty
Disciple prohibited picky eaters
I'm not your disciples
Enough talk fast food
Do not
How to say you do not eat, then ...
What do you want
I'll slip into your mouth
Stop point to be gentle bear thorough
You know it bear thorough
This bear children as soon as possible to go back into him
What the people do run
Hate you
I wait for the next nine too
Nine too?
stop
Who when your disciple ah
Stop you bastard
Where to run
Export export it ...
Awaited
Brother, you want to eat it
Ah so I'll eat a oh
First to an orange
Right or forget
Still have the first bite to eat cherries
Look Jiro pill is the father
Oh Dad
Ichiro Jiro Yan pill you have a good practice it
Yes
Father urged me to invite you to practice
Of course, although not immediately teach
Master
I would have taken a little time to wait you can do
Oh and this is
Ok
I'm sorry
Toru Bear
Yo pig Wang Shan
I heard that you are separated for such a long time and finally received disciples ah
Yes, ah, but suddenly the guy on the run no shadow children
did you see
Nearly so high child
Child?
Obviously you just like a child
You cut really long-winded ah
It is I, as a father of two opinions
Inexperienced you are not being a good guardian
Ah eh
I mean it is a temper
More important is nine too
He really kinda flexible
Human children child really is ...
You say humans?
Do you feed the disciples are human children
Master
Sore let go ah
Humanity?
Why would our world
Humanity? It is human?
Why have humans here
Nine too
Wait Bears Toru I say you do not want to hear
The child quickly put children back into its original place
How, ah just one or two human Bale
You and we may not know
But why should we monsters and humans living in different worlds
So weak is because human beings are their dark hearts parasitic
If darkness is parasitic in trouble
dark? Ha ha
That kid's heart can not see that kind of stuff
Listen to me, this is not your personal problem
My disciples by myself to deal with
Listen give you a word of advice
Even for everyone astringent days Street Stop it
For everyone?
You really think you are new to master yet pig King of the Mountain
what?
Then use your power to see if you can stop me ah
Here's the problem altogether is also here a resolve to forget
Wang Shan pigs and bears Toru duel ah
Waiting for this moment a long time
Fast to make a place for
To decide the new master yet
Then pulled back a little
Bravo
Bear Toru calm
Good eh on the ah ah!
I bet to win the King of the Mountain Pig
I also pressed pig Wang Shan win
I also pressed pig King of the Mountain
This does not have to bet no thing
Really
father
You retire
What is the attitude that bears Toru ah
Do not understand the etiquette
You look down on us right bastard
Wang Shan pig a lot to learn
Ah well abide by the rules
That guy there really any rules ah
That jerk
The audience have become the enemy
Then the two of them want to cut it
Sword master is prohibited adult
Everyone with a rope guard and scabbard tied pull it out of the
So ah
Station Stop brats
Where are you
This in the end is what ah fool
This is the guy provocation ah
Indeed the King of the Mountain Pig
You just do the same thing
Hit
idiot
hateful
Come back again
father
do not worry
Note
Sumo term audience cheering
There is room for doing it
Look out!
Wang Shan Pig is overruled
To determine the winner yet
Wang Shan refueling ah pig
Wang boar pig boar Wang Shan Wang
Wang Wang boar pig boar Wang Shan ...
No one ... no one giving him refuel
That guy is alone a person ah
Wang boar pig boar Wang Shan Wang
Wang Wang boar pig boar Wang Shan ...
hateful
You like to continue anyway
You do not win will not give up
Stop it
how come
Come back again
Wang Wang boar pig boar Wang Shan ...
Ah ah on the play there
Kill his father
Toru Bear
Do not lose ah
who is it
Even someone to bear Chejia oil
Who is Who
Do not lose ah!
nine…
Won
So far
Guru adults
What are you doing it
Now a test from earlier
I have not decided to become what God does
Guru adults
Please bear thorough punishment to mankind brought in
But even if you want to punish
He has not been playing you get on the ground yet
No matter how ... whoever says
Nine too are my disciples
Appears to be well awake
Do you want to set a precedent it
Although very poor, but I do not think can afford to bear this responsibility Toru
I have to assume responsibility
After all, he received barely disciples is the old lady ah
But his heart was dark in case the parasitic words
Does not mean that a person will all be swallowed by darkness ah
but
Why are you so thoroughly cover bear it
Call it a day to dissolve
Xiong thanked the master Toru good adult generosity bar
hateful
Well you strong
Have seen it
If you follow the words really become strong
I do your disciples row
Well anyway, you will escape it
The warranty period it also
Delicious
Le nine good too
I'll exercise your consciousness to do it
Oh, very fit nine too
Enough talk
Well good look next action
Pretty Pretty
Understand me understand practice soon
You make me practicing ...
Nine too Come
Ah Tengteng pain
Next stop
To ... to correct where
Ha said he wanted to change ... a good laugh
This is no way, after all, it is the first thing
The first time I was the first time
To shut up
This is Off Speaking Exercise can do Enhancing
A good scratch explain
explain?
This is a task master is not it
Hopeless
First ah woo ah Hold the sword
Shua ah then waved to boom
understood?
Eh ... it was so?
I say it is ...
Woo ah ah Hold the shabu to wave and then boom
understood?
Wow ... wow ground?
Woo is not ah
Woo ah
No no right
Woo is babble
Woo ... babble
No no No no
It is Woo
Yeah Woo
No no No no right
Woo babble ah
Woo ah ah
No no No no
It's completely wrong
How savvy you so bad
Who can do this ah
what?
How you might learn that teaching would be ah
Do Jijiwaiwai fast train
I do not practice
Fast train
hateful
Nine beginner or too little detail you again ah
Know it
Then carefully taught the ah
To hold in the hearts of the sword ah
Some of you right in the heart of the sword
What? There's no such thing ah
The sword is the heart of the most important ah
Here's here
Understand the practice soon
Fast train
cut
Where are you going
This guy is how the case ah
Always howling stretch of
Bear Bear Toru Toru etc.
Well what sword ah fool hearts
Ah you better hurry up and go home
Said that the disciples did not five or ten years into things
Half-consciousness that point you may learn better how ah
Just needed something to eat, then
Or hurry back to the human world is better
Here can be no place for you
Understand, then hurried away on its own
That guy does
I do not know
Although there are two three days will not come back but ...
Would you please tell me exactly what to do disciples
First sweeping laundry cooking
Suddenly you how the
Because of what happened yesterday it
It's nothing
Leave him the guy who is easy to top
But the next day they will all forget their silly ran back
Instead, he was concerned to find their own unpleasant
Said that not a
That would hang again throw a little wrinkle
I was the first time to sell things to the human ah
Is that right
You want to stay here when
Who knows
What is it really unpleasant
It's really no way to get humans
You bastard humans
You monster asshole
But I heard Dad say
Humanity will quickly become difficult to clean up
I must take now up to us to pick up him
Fast Stop Jiro pill
brother
How so small people could become a monster ah
After my brother and if they do what things too much
And even though I speak
I taught him
If you snitch, then I can not let you
Jiro enough pills
I saw those soft foot shrimp to gas
Hello my brother, but very powerful
Taking the same can be like fairy make things float up oh
Let the guy experience it
Not work
Power is not used to posters but to do good
Father does not always say do
Although I was only a child
But I'll practice
One day will be like his father did
Grow a long nose and huge teeth
A powerful swordsman
I also want
I have become like my father handsome swordsman
Come on
Ok
Handsome handsome ah
"So small people" do
hateful
Ok? This is how the case ah
So and so is unauthorized sweep
Your disciples dry ah
Do not give me to do extra things
That is how you hurt
What a shame
Been hit you do not feel embarrassed
Really
I was very weak indeed very shameful
Just like you said
You know like
Let me also say that it
So what you ah
what?
The man you have to get up early every day but sleep until noon
The man you have been busy busy doing nothing
So obviously busy but do nothing
That man is the king of the mountain it means pig
Though the man has been very busy but attentive
You obviously very busy but always so-so
what do you want to say in the end
You can not win that person can be considered to understand the reasons I
You say what you brats
Stop you give me to try again
You said several times this guy will do the worst!
Both of you calm down
Ah how you think you are talking with the master
Master's words are on a good way to make a master ah
Because a little thing to get angry
Hey
One can not escape no matter resolved soon
Dare to give me advice you kid really have the guts ah
but…
Just shut up and listen to the disciples on the line
I do not want it
If you listened to the words of a fool will be infected
Give me to shut up brats
Noisy dead fucker
Nine would forgive him too
This is not the man ah
So you do not care about the atmosphere point
Bear Toru we go outside to go outside
Let me go let me go
Hateful hateful hateful
Anyhow, I am also in earnest to do
But he considered that what ah brats
Almost be all right? Go quickly put him back
I do not say it idle
I also have to do the drywall cut firewood to earn money picking what
Also earn his share of the money
That does not stop quickly enough, right hand
Why I would want to be the guy to make irresponsible remarks
You think so right
you're right
You should understand how easily the single state as before it
Singles these days ah
Do not have to bear any responsibility nothing trouble
Even if it is telling the truth there is no need to get angry
Ah give something away
So late still exercise can really admire ah bear thorough
Grandmaster
Side show to their own efforts to see the disciples
Let him learn good too
Ah ... yes I think so too
Ok as a reward I give this to you
What's that
Oh letter of introduction
letter of introduction?
With his disciples to go to various countries around it
With this it is easy to see around the Guru
That are all well-known Sage ah
Certainly understand what is really powerful Oh
but…
So I wish you a pleasant journey
Obviously is a good opportunity to get rid of the kid
But adults guru said so bad refused ah
too slow
Too slow is too slow is too slow
hateful
Please you eat slowly eat
I venture to ask
In the end what it called strong
Although little old lady strength
But you see, I can make the illusion
Do not underestimate it Oh,
Hallucinations sometimes more realistic than reality
This is
That is
The so-called strong
What powerful
Why do you want to pursue that kind of stuff
Little old lady though Psychic
But no matter how strong their own how to show off
There are things that can not be beat
This is
That is
Young really sorry ah
It can help the old lady rubbed his waist
Psychic back pain does not work ah
It hurts bitterly
powerful
Then you should not ask decrepit
Decrepit but regardless of wind or rain
Just sitting here just like a stone
why
Forget time forget things
Even forgetting itself
In order to go beyond reality
This means that
That is
Turned to stone the
powerful?
Naturally, I am very open ah
Faster than the others catch prey
Tasted delicious world who is the winner
When the time comes it can catch enough
This means that
That
There are flaws
Rest assured I will not eat the guests
Check it out
Listen to these stupid things just disoriented
Also came close to being eaten
Even his body has lost out of it
There are many powerful meaning of it
Each Sage made it very interesting
Then have to sit at the table to learn it
So it makes more sense to do it
At least not like a person, like a place
Wow what barking Awu
Rely on your own sense of what to find ah
Obviously he can not explain
It is your perception bad
You teach bad
You tear each other to force the energy used up it also touches on how
Give me a break I have exhausted
Do not sleep
I was not really can not afford to ah
Do you care
He said I bad perception
I do not think so
Whether clothes or sweeping
The beginning you do not understand anything
Little guide us immediately to grasp the essentials
Frank endeavored
Remember things quickly
but
There is a problem bear thorough
Look at his tricks
Simply chaos stretch ah
That is the original too
why
Because that guy no parents and no master
Are on their own to become strong
Really become strong
This is his talent but also his misfortune
Who, then he does not listen
Can not put forward a decent proposal to others
So ah
But sometimes heard him say
Feel suddenly
What can you feel it
To find their own meaning to the phrase you
Correct
I think there is some truth
I do not know in the end you want to teach people how ah
Odyssey Bear thorough adults
Actually so persistent to that kid actor ah
It was not
Say annoying words
You're a kid actor, when he is also comparable with
Obviously so weak mouth but stiffened
At that time only because there is no decent master
In addition to the master adults
No one takes you seriously do
Say you are disobedient and troublesome guy
Soon resign
hateful
A group of verses disgusting bad guy
Really
And now you do exactly the same
But although I think the best kind of kid quickly disappear
But if you intend to continue to do his master
Think about it
When you were a kid actor in the end what you want
good night
Meaning to themselves to find ah
Really do not understand
This is the Qi can learn oh
Not do it
Will succeed
To successfully target
Just you talking?
Will succeed
I'm doing ah
Society should at least step
Bitterly pain ...
how
what are you doing
Will succeed
To successfully target
You engaged in what ah
You look down on me now
It did not
That is why you
none of your business
Hello Fana
pain…
People do
He in the end is really like doing ah
Is simply a mother duck and ducklings do
I'm not a duck
Children learn to grow up like their parents
It is taken for granted
I'm not the parents
He is going to start from scratch to learn from you the
Like parents of a baby chasing
baby
Bear Toru This guy is not no thing
Although often said that no parents because the child's imitation unhappy
But what ...
Hey kid
What time are you going to continue referred ah
Such words just imitate joke is becoming not strong
Hey do not get in the way
Not enough for him before you bother you
Line Go to hell
Hey guy when it started getting out of ah
Who knows
Outspoken disciple may feel it is too cute
That bastard did not ...
real or fake
So how about this trick
Ah come
A little pause pause
Without a pause
Hey give me back so much more
Without you
And so again
strange?
I obviously did not see him
Able to understand
Can understand
hateful
Give it a try
it hurts
How nine too
You do ah
stop
In the end how the
Nine too you ...
I have always just looked at his footsteps learning
Unwittingly caught on to his next step
What are you kidding
Really is too great ah nine
The first think you do commendable
Bear thorough you'd better come with nine Imperial College school
what did you say
Why do I want him to learn
You can also teach oh
relatively
Sword grip and I do not understand boxing
So teach me
Damn it hurts
You can not be serious
pain
To keep an eye on the opponent cater opponents
cater
pain
Bear thorough guy
After all, in spite of a self-centered around the guy
Cater to what the opponent is good at what he does best
This alone is his own side effects become strong ah
pain…
To cater to the opponent
I cater to pain ... ah
Obviously there is no
You drag ass
Seriously teach me again
pain
hateful
Do not get carried away
I bet Jiro pill
me too
See trick to see trick to see trick to see trick to see trick
Hello strong ah
I like a strong guy
Next to my house and play
I have a lot of delicious desserts oh
So come play
done
hateful
Say a little slower ye eat
I won all the things packed up
hateful
Taller a lot of it
Well one hundred is Mr.
Mr. lot
What a long time
real or fake
It has a kind of mold
Yes
Luckily he can really develop into human children do so
That you find it
Growth is more thorough bear it
After so much practice movements become faster
indeed
I do not know in the end who is the master of it
Nine so how old are you
So ah
From now on you too is the seventh
Nine on the list too
Toru Bear Master Please take me as a disciple it
I also imagine that becomes too strong nine Mr.
Not bad good consciousness
Thank you
Then you go there right line
Getting ready to present it in the side of the tail
Are some kid actor
Not like the way ah can taught
My own training myself to decide
Not for me to decide
Nine is already too adult
Treated like adults treat him
This guy hair no longer a few
I have long hair
where
Hey
I won
Goodbye
and many more
I have not finished yet
Wash bowl oh
Stop you bastard
Nine too
Come to my house and play
stop
Nine it is really great too
His blessing bear thorough care home it is very lively
We do not see the group back in here swinging
Bear thorough ...
Do not take the kind of half-baked and father than
How, ah brother
It's nothing
Where the
It's really annoying guy
here is
Key ... together?
That ... is from a long time ...
I ask how this idea
whale
Whale ah
Did not I say Well
Said to you
Do not care
Noisy dead
Hey
Bye
Who is this
what happened
To downtown, then go outside downtown
Go outside to do what it will do
That is your freedom
Come on
This guy from the first grade when it is annoying
We have been ignored
Ah so that what she is doing it all right
Hey do not run ah
stop
On the outside, then do anything right
Will not trouble to others of
do not move
you saw it?
Minor disputes just friends
You saw nothing, right
hateful
So what you face
What guy dressed ah good soil
Come on
School we all get along very well that is a lie
Violence is bad
But thank you for helping me
I did not help you
You obviously helped me ah
What this study
I do not know anything
From elementary school after never been to school
really
The word on the book that I have to teach you
Well I called maple
Maple wood wind
My name is Lin
Lotus word ...
Soji head even add to it
Correct
lotus
Break on through to the ...
Nine too
Noisy dead
too slow
Do not call it
Nine too
Out early
He seemed quite busy latest
What are you doing ah
Hero ready to take away their own foot abominable whale Revenge
But in fact the hero is not to fight it with their own
Yourself?
That whale is reflected in his face in the mirror
mirror
Good attention is focused so soon be able to unlock my reference problem
Maple teach well
Master a little long-winded right
You say your master is raising kendo master it
Master waste wood
Your relationship nice
How could we meet on the old quarrel
Nice envy
why
I have not had a fight with their parents
I am happy to live in their parents
From kindergarten beginning has been exam
Vow to test out the parents expect results
But both of them did not understand my feelings
Not at all aware
but I know
I have to rely on their own to discover the true self
So now how hard to be hard to learn
If you can avoid fees grades in college, then
I ran away from home
Only then will be able to start their own learning
Single-handedly graduation
And then lived up to life
First speak their minds with others
More readily
maple
Na About the book
I teach a limited range
There must be more to teach you a method teacher
Lin do you want to go to college
How can it be
Go to the exam, then I will support you
But I can not go to college
You do not want to know more about what you do not understand
miss you
High recognize
Have identified the extent of such a system of graduation exams
Formerly known as Big Unit
Even aside from high school are also eligible for the university entrance exam
Not do it
Eh?
Although you do not know how to learn
But from then on, then no schooling
First, from the evening started
This troubled world can not be so simple
Even if there is no guardian who admitted the tuition
Now you get the scholarship will not lend you money right
But that
I understand
Really impossible to college ah
Sorry
I talked about good
There are a lot of special university system to be born
You do not pay back the money can introduce business scholarship
Of course, it also depends on results
Thank you
thank you
Math and science are compulsory courses
I never learned exactly
Gave them to me I'll try to teach you
High recognize the need to attend the exam resident card
But old resident certificate is no longer applicable
Really the case
But the household registration records can be attached to the ticket has to register new residents permit
Please confirm your father's current address is correct
Separate long-father?
Did not know where he is
But can be found in simple words
To see him do
Might as well just go suddenly inviting trouble
He may also have forgotten me
but
What should I write
Dad gave me the ball
Guests things that you did not take
Really do not accidentally forget
thank you so much
blunt
do you remember me
really
excuse me
lotus
You do lotus
Even big now
I do not know
Where were you so long
So that someone take care of me
Great you can without incident
Sorry so far not been able to do for you
father
Is not it great
Father is a long time later that her mother's things
He has been looking for my missing
After the police give up and kept looking for
is it
maple
That man is Feng boyfriend
Not at all
Who that is otherwise
Which school
Orgy to stay
Sorry
After that I can become ordinary people do
ordinary?
And ordinary people with their parents
Common learning work
Common home to ordinary sleep
Maybe I could have that kind of living law
But you confuse it
Master side of things?
I have something to talk to you seriously
How about training
Listen to me actually
Do you want to be lazy
Listen to me bear thorough
What is that compared to
In your bed to find me explain
I think human school
What?
I want to know the other world so
More important than that you have to do it
Your goal is not to strong yet
I have become strong
Ha? Less funny
Toru Bear
I have a very strong
Which you stronger
And will always talk to you this way become
I will not listen to the words of her own call out
Tell me when you become strong ah
Forget it
And so you go
I have a word to say to you
My father found
I'll go there now decided
Allowed to go
Step aside
I will not let you go
Allowed to go
Nine too
Confusing thing solved yet
It seems not ah
Been okay
I will meet my father met can be solved
Is not it a bit reluctantly himself
I did not need reluctantly
Today, I would have been in the library
What can I do to come
wrong
No no No no
Word to the wise should understand it
Sorry
Do not apologize for anything
I am sorry
Forget it
One of the two really are so
His father would appear at this time
Do not really back yet
It can not come back
Nine is not too bear thorough change back to the waste wood ah
Does not have a scrap wood
What are you doing very dangerous ah
Even guys like him
Also has been in the family too when nine ah
On his?
hateful
lotus
Today dinner is ham board
Dad did eat together
Speaking about the person you care for has been
Can you tell me more detail it
Eh?
Then you must look good to greet and thank him
Then two people live with it
Well? What is it for granted
That would not schedule so tight ah
is it
That is not what i mean
Yes
Adults and children time to time is not the same as it
For me and my mother had lived with you just like yesterday
yesterday
Sorry for suddenly I changed a little bit
Forget the bitterness of the past so far
After the restart it
What does it mean to re-start
Why do you think it is the bitterness of
Dad, you know what I
Do not understand anything let alone what is now know like
Lin I was ...
Of course you do not know
Because I did not say anything
Today, I'm sorry I'm not going
Rice it
no need
After you decide how to do just fine
But do not forget
Father can do for you to go all out
I'm doing ah
Why that's the case with his father
Allowed to go
Why think of that nasty guy
Start again
hateful
Allowed to go
I do not know
That is
Most hated
The most annoying
Me in the past
hole
Terrifying a face
Seemed like a lotus
Tell me in the end is what
A person or a monster
monster?
Or ugly monster
You say
tell me
You say I in the end
Lin you not quite right
I was in the end
I
I sometimes have a very, very painful
Like incurable
What do you want to feel the hearts gushing
More than you more than me
Certainly we all are like this
So it does not matter
and so
never mind
Wait for the
This is my favorite childhood books Bookmarks line
I saved a lot of times it was
If you feel yourself very dangerous when there is that kind of feeling like just
When the amulet
What ah what happened
Nine too
Come to my house
Guru adults suddenly decided the date
On the city rose up
date?
Slow oh
thanks Mom
Tomorrow is my father and thy master decisive day
Determine the new master race
you do not know
In fact, we played a little point of dispute
There was a time not a little embarrassed to see him
is it
But I have not seen his father
Has been busy training
Although there is no way a little lonely
You do not want to lose it own master
Not to mention what it would be awkward for him to cheer
Anyway we are all friends
of course
If good game just fine
Ok
Jiro pill
brother
Do not wrap too long people will give nine too trouble Oh
You have been listening to the evening bell rang
I send you right to the door
Thanks, bye
What wonderful game
The outcome has been decided outset
Human and bear thorough as you half-baked
I understand that duty to the half-baked
Ichiro Yan
Why like me
why
Which team do you support
Choose which team it
I chose the pig Wang Shan
I chose bear thorough
I chose ah Chousi person
I am very troubled
It has been nine years have been unhappy or unhappy worry
Finally decided
When it decided to do what God
Put bluntly determination of God
Conduct reincarnation ceremony after the race
Stay tuned
Now proceed to wade days Street Guru battle ceremony
Candidate who came
Light from the disciple's face can clearly see the advantages and disadvantages of the ah
Nine in the better too
Do not frown ah bear thorough
Immediately contested ah
Noisy dead
According to the rules to use the filled sheath knife
Allowed Choudao
Runaways for the loser
Within ten seconds of one of them is still in a coma loser
Other places have rules
The two sides prepare
Start
One up on this trick
Bear in Toru brave
That guy does not consider the physical
Shut up looking good
You see
Indeed the father of an adult
Situation is not good ah
Just keep being beaten
This…
It seems the outcome has been fixed ah
You would not do it bear thorough
one
two
three
four
Fives
six
hateful
Seven
Eight
Nine too
nine…
Toru Bear disciple
it's him?
Nine too
Come on nine too
Give courage to bear it Toru
What are you doing ah idiot
I quickly stood up
You guys obviously are gone
Dare to casually appear here
You're like how a lost dog
What you say you bastard
a shame
All this time
Do not quarrel
Give me why they always like this
Do a drooping
You go quickly to win the game
Do not you long-winded
I will not lose
what
To fight it
Seems to get interesting
right
Back comeback
Do it in the middle
Look, guys laughing
Is the expression and practice with when nine too
Could it be that obviously in the game
That guy's heart has been detached from the immediate rival
Can be said to be completely focused not my situation
Only bear a thorough person, then there is no chance of winning
but
Two people hard to say
Dad refueling
Ah going to lose
To shut up
brother
Nine too
That guy mere humans
Do not be suppressed
Fight back
Take out your strange force
Is here
On ah
one
two
three
four
Fives
six
Seven
Eight
nine
ten
The outcome has been fixed
Bear thorough wins
Do not let people live in fear ah
I did not want you to worry about me
You can win real loss
Of course, win
nonsense
Were beaten rickety
Talkative
The new master was born
Viva Viva
What a good son
gone
sword
Missing
What is this red
Nine too
what happened
father
My father read the power of the sword plus decide the outcome
You won
How that could win your dabbler
It is nine too
right
Stop Ichiro Yan
father
I'll send him on his way
Look
Nine did not see too
Deserve
Listen
Victor was my father pig Wang Shan
Who would agree with this darn thing
That ... that is what
hole
Must not be too ah nine
How dare you
Do not accept nine too dark
Stop nine too
so terrible
Nine too
you
Darkness is eroding Koizumi Yan
Inexcusable
brother
where are you
What are you sleep
Up ah
Nine too
Slow
Slow slow slow slow
Started training
How can seven
Sorry Ichiro Yan
Ichiro Yan that is by no means a monster telekinetic
That obviously is hosted in the human heart of darkness
Power generated
Guru adults
You've already noticed yet
Wang Shan Pig
Say everything out of it
His parents must be something hiding something right
I decided to raise him without telling everyone
Although I know people will have dark
But I think I was raised by the words should be fine
Now think about is my bragging
I was too arrogant
Why am I not grow like a father tooth yet
do not worry
One day grow out
Why is my nose does not like his father elongation
do not worry
That time will be the
What is my father ...
You are my son Ichiro Yan
Not others
But I
Wang Shan pig's son
The more so that he believes he is the son of a monster
The more he does not trust himself
But increased dark hearts
I did not expect air monster world
Make holes in the human heart becomes so large
What is dark
I did not understand so stupid
I do not know where it came from brother
For me, my brother is a brother
Jiro pill
Guru adults
We have been unable to live together and Ichiro Kazuhiko yet
Unable to start all over again yet
Ichiro Yan now must still be somewhere
If not get rid of the darkness from the hearts, then Ichiro Yan
Everything will be undone
You have to leave it bear thorough
idiot
Do you want to go to avenge
What can do such a thing
Hey patchouli Square
I can not put up with
If you think I've always been a good way would be wrong
You have not seen a bear thorough as it can grow the slightest memory
You idiot
Even so you also want to do
Thank you for your teachings
Thanks for letting me be able to stand tall
But I'm not going to take revenge
I like Ichiro Kazuhiko
If I were wrong step will become his appearance today
The reason I did not become
Thanks to the raising of my people
Mr. lot
Mr. hundred
There we
Nine too
you…
So I can not ignore
Ichiro Yan problem is my problem
and so
I have to go
That guy
It please you
understood
We know your awake
We'll take care Toru Bear
We will take care of him,
So you go
Go
"I brought up the people" do
We actually have been enumerated,
From nine too little time has been together
The beginning is a arrogant and annoying children
Rain or shine
Tirelessly day bother to take care of him
He has never expressed to us gratitude
And other recovered
He long so big
Always boast
very impressive
amazing
Toru Bear
lotus
Tokyo stock market today
The Nikkei Stock Average rose slightly
In a few days ago the New York stock market
Average fell
The Nikkei Stock Average rose to the highest value
Hope you can help me keep what
what happened
I must have made a break opponents
Do not know can not win
Loses the case may be the end of everything
how come
Can you recognize really good
Thanks to you
I know a lot of things did not know
I truly recognized world wide
what are you saying
We also future
You can learn together
I am very happy
So I want to say thank you
and many more
I do not want
I do not like this
Nine too
Inexcusable
Mere humans
Actually in this place
That is
Too dangerous to run away
What are you doing brisk walking ah
I will not let go
Damn
Full gallop
Hide farther
Shoot it in TV
lotus
Damn not here
Have to find a place
whale
Danger
Do not go there
Fear
Is that?
whale?
Alighted from the vehicle
Faster
Fear ah
run
maple
How to defeat that guy ...
This side
Where to go
How to do
In order to compete with that thing
Open my empty heart
Then his mind off all the dark inside
With a sword through himself and his world disappeared from it
I can do only these yet
me
Just from the beginning has been thinking
Why hold your hand
Run up together
I'm obviously not afraid
why
I think of it
Began to experience a Lin
Time and learn together
I am very happy
Because no one would be so happy to learn
to be with you
I also have the courage to strive
So now, too
If you want to continue the fight
I will follow along
Do not forget
Whenever we are not a person in combat
maple
Play emergency notification
Since the fire broke out near the Shibuya station
The train will be temporarily stay ...
What this motion is?
Ichiro Yan in pursuit nine too
In human runaway street
While the impact of each other and our world
But actually such a big impact too ...
This Human fight
Why should we have to roll into non
Originally Let mankind enters our world is a mistake
Hey Toru Bear
Freeze you'll die ah
You are not allowed to walk ah
Less long-winded
Things I've heard
I must try to do something I have to ...
Toru Bear
What are you like this now can do ah
Guru Now only you can do something
You can then use that method
You said method?
What way
While nine too intend to face a man
But he now needs help from others
I was a half-bastard
Even though I wanted to help the guy
Let me fill in missing his heart
This is my half-baked
The only way to do the
Since you say so ...
This guy ah
I own the rights to transfer reincarnation
To reborn as God?
That monster can not generally be done
That is why only the Guru can ...
just now…
Toru Bear is master
Listen bear thorough
Once you have decided there is no way regret
So you can do
can
Now I see the eyes clear and bright as a mirror without hesitation
Ichiro Yan
Disappeared
hateful
Danger
Maple Run
The guy came at me
maple
What do you want to do?
The hatred of Shredded crushing
Trampled underfoot
With the power to suppress the other would meet?
Although you have a huge look askew
But it just obsessed with revenge human Bale
Who both
The hearts of everyone has a dark place
There I also have lotus
We carries darkness
Desperately struggling
and so…
Lin is not lost
You simply fell in this dark man
We will not lose to you
maple
lotus
no solution anymore
Ichiro Yan Look
Put your darkness brought it all
lotus
Could it be that…
And I disappear with it
lotus
Can not lose
Nine too
It is a bear thorough
He reincarnated God ninety-nine
It became the ōdachi
this is
That guy
you idiot
I'll be the sword in your heart
Heart sword?
Some bars sword hearts
You have that kind of thing
Jian heart is very important
Beats like a drum
look forward
More like a
So now you are "nine too."
Well nine too
I'll exercise your consciousness to do it
Nine too
What an idiot you cry cry
I Zuifan this guy bawl
Noisy dead I did not cry
Be careful
Nine too
lotus
Not enough
Bao Jianfeng from tempered
That is
Instant jump
Ichiro will exhibit a prototype Yan
if that is the case…
Seize the moment
Do not hesitate aimed at him
It's now
Charge
Success ... yet
No
Obviously is a human ...
Ichiro Yan
You and me
The Foster grew up by the monster
Son is a monster
This in the end is ...
where?
Mom and Dad
Jiro pill
So far what I have to do it ...
I like to go to the arena and everyone
It's nine too ...
Listen nine too
Once I decided that this would not give up the character
If you hesitant, but I will beat you
Noisy dead I will not hesitate to
That's good
You looked at me quietly
Let me see the next bar
Yesterday Tokyo Shibuya
Unmanned runaway large trailers
Large explosion occurred
Refuge when someone fall break
Most of the injured people have fled
Finally are minor
It is understood the accident before the police
There report said, "saw the shadow of whales."
There are many people report
Explosion-proof camera does not have any record ...
Good looking
That too is nine
Began as a weak child
That
If you practice daily efforts
One day will be able to work independently
maybe
Because bear thorough
I missed the opportunity reincarnation of God
When they come back to the master
OK OK
Today is nine too congratulations feast
The Cheers
Look at that
The girl was nine and a supporter too
maple
Why are you here
I was invited to the
Ah this
Lost his way
Finally looking back
Well back to you
thank you
This is a high recognition of the application
High recognize
Higher graduate qualification test, exam recognized by the high, it is considered a high school equivalent, and can take the exam
How to also intends to test it
How about you pick it
I want to test
awesome
I knew you'd like this
All work together
Fireworks friends
After the nine days of street involved too left
Did not pick up the sword again
But he was a powerful swordsman than anyone else
Chest called the bear thorough sword
The only swordsman
If that guy
No matter how difficult things in the face
Will be a success across
Great lotus
- Provides - Xia Jiong subtitles group
Mast shi ta holds an nn su center have head の wo?
Mast beast's head
Yin shi hold っ ta San Tan Chong Shi left Circular で ru?
Hidden shotgun shot down
This degree ko そ hesitate NADO se zu ni?
For once I would like to hesitate
そ の cited ki wo cited ki ta い gold?
That pulled the trigger
Thou い の zu wa false positive body Sakae heart ??
It is the true face of vanity?
Wo fear of failure made me cry ru terror heart ??
Fear ... fear of failure?
Ge ra me cry on hold ち ki floating Adachi ~ te?
Exalted shaken
Ga っ ta pride swelling on me cry ??
Inflated self-esteem?
Connecticut basic guarantee for the whole mess re ta wo え breathing?
Well rectify uneasy breathing
Refers to consciousness ni te wo set Circular い ku?
Set consciousness fingertips
Servant da ke ga row was from World で gun sound boom ga ku?
Only the roar of gunfire in the world I could go
Dizzy い い Meng Qu flash ga ke te い っ ta?
A dazzling flash across the bleak
"He ga ka wa ri ma ta final where ka ga beginning ma ru san da"?
"What is the end of what will have new life."
U-ki そ っ と そ の light wa ni そ servant called u san で ru?
Yes, that beam of light must do this to me shouted
Circular chase い interrogate holds an nn su center have ta の head の Austrian ni?
Depths of desperate beast's eyes
Lonely と pure Sui wo see pay was from Connecticut?
Find solitude and pure
Scotia te ra re ta ta い child cat Mi ni?
Like abandoned kitten
Body cowardly e te wo Circular ru pill?
Curled up with fear
Thou basic guarantee ko ma ma as have bu の で い で system?
Like with a rope tied with
Shi te ra used to feed い と ku ko na ra ta ga out?
If you can tame words
Zu mo ku い の と possibility limb election Ze Tong ma ni me cry?
Surrounded by a myriad of options and possibilities in
Exploration shi te ta ta mo の で hope san ga bo ya ke te い ku?
Had been looking for, hoping things had become blurred
"He made me cry ma ma ka ta ga born Ho ka ga dead san da san で い ku"?
"What is there anything newborn died."
そ っ と そ ko u-ki kara wa wa me cry escaped ge ra nai shi da ro u?
Yes, this is certainly not escape it
Wen had gi ya ka ru evening twilight?
So calm evening
Mayonaka の silence?
The night silence
Ma ta holds an nn su center have ga da su storm made me cry?
Beast riots
U servant wa そ っ と interest wo kill shi?
I quietly hold your breath
Dan Dan warehouse ni wo Circular ru includes the postage?
Bullets into the magazine
Static kill ka na ko の Genki づ ka wo sense made me cry ち ぬ ma wa yo-u ni?
In order to prevent this murderous silence perceived
Today servant da ke mo ga row was from World で gun sound boom ga ku?
Now is the roar of gunfire only I can go in world
Dizzy い い Meng Qu flash ga ke te い っ ta?
A dazzling flash across the bleak
"He ga ka wa ri ma ta final where ka ga beginning ma ru san da"?
"What is the end of what will have new life."
Ko u shi te zu っ と ko の world wa meter loop ~ te ru?
So the cycle of world
"He ga ka wa ri ma ta final where ka ga beginning ma ru san da"?
"What is the end of what will have new life."
Ki っ と ki っ と
Must be sure
Support us and become VIP member
to remove all ads from OpenSubtitles.org